## **Nick Carr**

Highly energetic, personable and focused professional with a great history of working well within a team, and also leading others. I am always looking for something new to learn, a problem to solve or a way to better myself. I have 4+ years of international work experience.



### **Experience**

### 2017-03 - Sales/ manager

**2017-12** *AAC Travel* 

- -Attract customers to come to Australia on a package tour
- -create and maintain relationships with schools to create new leads and prospective clients
- -create itineraries for clients

### 2013-12 - Manager/ head teacher

2016-12

Summit Foreign Language School

Originally I was an ESL teacher, however I was promoted to head teacher/ manager after my first year. I was responsible for recruiting and training new staff, creation of course content, translating between teachers and parents, day to day management of the school and overall happiness of the staff.

## **Education**

## 2006-02 - Curtin University of Technology- Bachelor of Asian

2010-12 Studies and Commerce

My studies gave me the foundation to learn about other countries and cultures, as well as general commerce skills, including accounting, finance, marketing and management.

#### 2013-06 - Keats Mandarin School

2014-12

I progressed from beginner level Mandarin to advance level with a year and a half due to a strong passion for the language.



### **Additional Activities**

### 2016-02 - Gorkha Primary School

2016-03

ESL Teacher

Aiding in developing the English course for a school half destroyed by an earthquake in Gorkha, Nepal. I spent 6 weeks in a remote village where most of the infrastructure had been destroyed. Since I had a background in education, I did what I could and helped the local teachers, sharing with them my style of teaching.

# Interests

Travelling

Languages

Self Development

Health and Fitness

Cooking

Mnemonics



### **Personal Info**

#### **Phone**

0424100980

#### E-mail

nickjcarr88@gmail.com



**Skills** 

Communication

Teamwork

Leadership

Time Management

**Problem Solving** 

**Self Motivation** 

Languages

**English** 

Mandarin